Good morning.
So, we have arrived safely in Hyogo Prefecture!
Thank goodness!
Everyone,
Thanks for your hard work!
See you soon!
How's the transportation?
It was a bit of a crazy morning. A lot happened.
But it's still before rehearsal.
We're going to go over hair changes, not hair changes.
We're going to check the hair accessories.
So for now, I just had twin-tails made.
I'll do the bangs later.
I'll do it later.
Okay, bye-bye.
Here's Hyougo.
Wow!
Good morning. Today is the first day of the tour. I'm Kakogawa.
Oh, my God, I'm still skinny. I'm still skinny too.
I'm still covered, too.
Shall we clap? A fandé?
Oh, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Let's do our best.
I'll do my best.
Cute. Cash outfits, seriously.
They all have boobs.
Oh, bro.
♪ Music ♪
Can you see this much?
It's not pretty at all.
Not at all.
Oh!
Oh, there's a lot of stuff here.
Thanks for the energy drink.
Oh, there are dorayaki, too!
So this is you.
What's this?
It's sticky. Ayu is it.
Ogra, green tea, lemon, strawberry, cream. Cold?
Cream puffs!
Cream puffs, too.
Oh, there's so many!
Oh, I know, I have to get some.
Cream puffs. What flavor?
Matcha, ogula, lemon. Let's go for it.
I'll have this one.
Bon appétit.
Yum! Yum!
Look! It's so custardy.
It's amazing! So much!
So much!
I'll eat it!
This is so good!
Na Na Na Na Na Na Na Na Na Na Na Na Na Na Na Na Na Na Na Na Na Na Na Na Na Na
We got snacks! Look!
Oh, no, no, no, no. Your forehead.
Why? I didn't even do my hair.
Clean forehead. Clean forehead?
I think I'll just do it then.
Smooth.
Anago sushi looks delicious.
What? "Anago sushi" sounds delicious.
I love little conger eel! I love little conger eel I want to eat young eel
Fugu Takumi
Fugutaku, I'm listening...
Norisuke, there's...
I don't know who that is
Whose turn is it?
What's that?
Anago zushi.
Norisuke!
Isn't this the real smile? Now that...
You're so good at smiling.
What? I'm listening.
I'm listening.
Give it to him.
Where did you find it? They're all lined up here.
This is Anago, isn't it?
Bye-bye, Mr. Anago.
Cream puffs.
Here's Lo.
He's early.
Okay, morning bubbles.
Yay cream puffs! I'll be back in the morning.
I don't mind.
Between you and me, cream puffs.
I ate them.
What a surprise!
But they don't know. That I ate this much.
Come here! Come here! Bye-bye!
Anago.
I said conger eel.
How's the conger eel?
He said it's ready to go.He said he was in preparation.
As expected.
Anago (conger eel).
They were delicious.
Anago. I did it.
Wasn't there someone else here?
Yes.
I'm Tara.
Bonito!
Bakamon!
Anagojishi.
Happy Yusho!
Let's all recharge our power!
Let's clap our hands loudly together!
Min-chan no isho!
I can't see much.
They were saying this about 3 years ago.
Isn't that it? Jeff Hayama.
One, two, one, two!
One, two!
Rock!
Something's coming!
One, what?
I got long pants.
This way.
You're looking dorky.
I've been told I'm tacky.
I've been getting my bangs done.
I'm so out of focus today.
Can you give me a second look?
Your posture's a little dark.
Yes, a little.
But it's not like we're...
With a dark posture.
Oh, man.
How's it going?
How's your day?
Great?
Yeah!
If the line weapon in the county buys again...
I got 50,000 yen.
I've been doing my makeup. What's that? There it is.
I did my makeup. I did it.
I'm going to surprise you.
Don't forget the surprise.
A surprise for everyone.
A song for everyone.
Because, right?
Here I go, I've done my makeup!
Done!
Today, the first day of the Hall Tour.
It's Half Twintail!
I turned 24 years old! Hey everyone!
Today, I took a picture in front of the hydrangea.
I took a picture in front of the hydrangea and posted it on Instagram, and to my surprise, my legs were crab-eaten in 7 places!
So today, it's itchy. The crab-eaten places...
I will do my best! Today's
Gotouchi Gourmet
Various kinds of cove pirinque and
and barreled pork belly, etc.!
I will eat a lot and do my best!
Please don't show me.
I made a mistake even in yellow!
More honey tea!
Blah, blah, blah.
I'll do my best!
My favorite is Kanamin.
I'll never bite!
Mmmmmm...
I won't bite.
Today's target announcer
A new one.
Okay, anyway.
Adult
Adult.
I say adult.
Today's theme is adults
Which means not a single bite.
I already said that.
It's my first time.
If I don't bite, I'm sure
I'll be able to pursue it in the future.
Oh, my God.
They'll quiz me on how many bites I've had.
It's just Pioli.
I don't bite.
Meow meow meow!
Don't be so nervous in the shadows.
I'm more nervous than I thought.
I'm nervous.
You're so nervous.
You're wrong, you're wrong, you're wrong.
Okay, I'll talk now.
Today, we're going to be talking about the Choki no Shusei's
Heart Rock On Hall Tour
2023.2023
You're just too cute and adorable.
Thank you for visiting us at
Thank you very much!
Oh!
Isn't she the cutest?
I'm Kanami!
This is my Kanami, Kanami Tsuchino.
She's amazing!
Except during lock-on free time
inside the venue
Photographing, recording
recording, etc.
strictly prohibited.
This performance is
For this performance
Cheering in your seat is allowed.
Oh, my gosh!
Yes!
Parentheses.
Please be sure to wear a non-woven mask when cheering.
Yay.
There is no limit to the time or loudness of your vocalizations in your seat, though,
Oooh.
Please refrain from shouting in a manner that may disturb the performance or inconvenience other patrons.
Sorry, sorry, sorry.
Skin jumping is prohibited.
It is forbidden to do anything that may be disturbing to other customers around you as well,
Please be careful.
In case of an emergency, please follow the unbendable posture,
Please evacuate the building.
Thank you very much.
I didn't bite.
One by one.
Almost.
So, I tried to sound mature at 24 years old,
How did you all feel?
I'm an adult.
So, it's the first day of the show.
Let's get excited together.
Are you ready to get excited?
The show will start in a few minutes.
Please look forward to it.
I don't have a name.
I was wondering about Japan at the end.
Kanami!
Junior!
Futoko!
Maruko!
Aki!
Hiyori!
Choteimeki Advertising Club!
Rock on!
Let's do it together!
Thank you for the encore.
I changed my clothes.
It's hot. I'm turning red today.
I'm at the train station until the very last minute.
It's Okunphy time and I'm coming to two times.
It's the first time in 2018.
Wow, oh, no.
19 years, huh?
I hope you're okay, already
I'm sweating so much
I'm off.
You surprised us all.
Surprised?
Good night.
That was fun.
First day of the tour!
Thank you for your hard work.
Yes, it's over. The first day of the tour in Hyogo is over.
It's over.
Thank you for your hard work.
The tour has finally started.
The tour has started.
It's been hot for 4 months,
It's already exciting, isn't it?
It's already hot.
It was crazy from the beginning.
And today is the day after Kanami's birthday,
There was also a surprise for Kanami.
Thank you very much.
We got a big cake.
That was amazing.
I really didn't know.
I was so surprised.
I'm glad.
We knew they were going to surprise us, too,
But we didn't know the details,
We didn't know when we were going to sing,
Herrin-chan sang,
It was pretty axial.
She was the axis.
I was wondering if I had untied my shoelaces or something.
In the meantime, I thought it would be better to talk longer,
She said it was really cool.
I thought you were going to sing with the first music.
Oh, yeah.Oh yeah.
It was hilarious.
It was the first time I heard a song that was quite challenging,
I'm glad it was that one.
I was surprised, but it was fun.
I have more memories.
Thank you very much.
Today is the Kyoto concert.
Rest and sleep well,
I will be ready for tomorrow.
I hope everyone will be ready for tomorrow.
It's already over.
When it's over.
The tour will continue,
Let's keep making fun summer memories together!
Bye bye!
Thank you very much.
You're doing fine.
Okay?
All right.
Knock knock.
Pervert.
Too much.
This one's not in the show, either.
He's wearing frilly pants.
She's cutting off her costume.
She's wearing frip pants.
He's going around.
Now...
What's this? Fripes?
I know you're in there.
What?
You know, I pushed the top flippant over here, and the skirt came out.
Oh, you noticed.
The skirt fell out.
Good girl, good girl.
So, are you going to turn around?
Yes, I will.
Subscribe to our channel!
I don't know why, but when I smile, it's like the world shines brighter.
I can turn my umbrella around and take it easy, because otherwise I wouldn't be able to walk.
I'm sure somewhere someone's crying, somewhere I'll get wet again, somewhere I won't get cold.
I'm sure that somewhere someone is crying because I want to share just a little bit of my feelings with them
I want to share just a little bit of my feelings with you, so I'll go wherever you take me
Goodbye, goodbye, thank you for yesterday After the rain, the cityscape turns color
On the canvas of my broken heart, a piece of the future is painted and blotted out
Goodbye, goodbye, thank you for yesterday After the rain, the streets turn color
I can say it now
Whenever you're lost, remember the reason for your tears
I'll try to smile even when it's raining
Come on, let's go wherever you want
Goodbye goodbye to yesterday's me
After the rain, the streets are sparkling
My heart is like a sunny sky, rainbow pools, making rainbow sounds
I play the rainbow piano
Goodbye goodbye to yesterday's me
After the rain, the streets are shimmering
My bent heart is like a flower, I'll let you play with my tears
I'll wear a rainbow dress
Words, music, arrangement by Miku Hatsune
Song: Hatsune Miku